/*quiz_data8 */

const questions = [
    {
//609問目
question:"finish(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["型","映画","終り","部門"],
correctAnswer: "終り"
    },
    {
//621問目
question:"arm(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["部分","腕","攻撃する","飲む"],
correctAnswer: "腕"
    },
    {
//635問目
question:"feature(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["医師","特徴","犬","技術"],
correctAnswer: "特徴"
    },
    {
//643問目
question:"official(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["堤防","態度、行動","箱","職務上の"],
correctAnswer: "職務上の"
    },
    {
//653問目
question:"worry(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["想定する","心配する","４分の１","声"],
correctAnswer: "心配する"
    },
    {
//663問目
question:"contain(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["負う","含む","特に","議論"],
correctAnswer: "含む"
    },
    {
//671問目
question:"plant(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["成功","植物","決定する","捕まえる"],
correctAnswer: "植物"
    },
    {
//677問目
question:"region(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["証明する","地域","治療","用意する"],
correctAnswer: "地域"
    },
    {
//682問目
question:"various(形容詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["さまざまな","板","はっきりと","度"],
correctAnswer: "さまざまな"
    },
    {
//696問目
question:"establish(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["仕事","設立する","在庫","貧しい"],
correctAnswer: "設立する"
    }
];

export default questions;

